<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PassLoc</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="to_be_logged_out">You are about to log out. Press the action button to confirm logout and disconnect from the database.\n You will be able to log in again via the login page.</string>
    <string name="logged_out_text">You have been logged out. Database connection interrupted.\nPress the action button to log in again.</string>
    <string name="not_logged_in">You have not logged in. Press the action button to login.</string>


    <string-array name="about">

        <item>PassLoc is an open-source password manager application that uses sql-cipher to store data on your device.</item>
        <item>Needless to say that all the data stored in the database are encrypted with strong and reliable encryption (AES256).</item>
        <item>PassLoc does not store any data on the cloud. Hence, this app does not require an internet connection to function.</item>
        <item>The source code can be found at github.com/mubashirtanveerayon/PassLoc .</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="encryption">

        <item>The database name is the name that is used to create the database with a unique extension(.loc) on your device.</item>
        <item>The database is first secured with a password you choose. After that, .</item>
        <item>Though the encryption algorithm uses several keys to encrypt your data the secret key is considered to be the mother key.</item>
        <item>Even if someone gains access to the password-protected database file they will not be able to decrypt your data without this key.</item>
        <item>This also means that if you happen to forget your secret key the database file becomes unusable.</item>
        <item>So, it is recommended to use a secret key that is actually secret(not like your contact number or date of birth) and that you can remember.</item>


    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ui">


        <item>In this version of the app most of the ui-interactions are done using the floating action button and the bottom navigation panel.</item>
        <item>Want a secret key suggestion? You can always use the <font color='blue'>unique password generator</font></item>
        <item>The access panel is for creating/logging into database files on your device.</item>
        <item>The view panel is for viewing the your saved password.</item>
        <item>The logout panel is used to logout/disconnect from database.</item>
    </string-array>




</resources>