<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PassLoc</string>


    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="to_be_logged_out">You are about to log out. Press the action button to confirm logout and disconnect from the database. You will be able to log in again via the login page.</string>
    <string name="logged_out_text">You have been logged out. Database connection interrupted.Press the action button to log in again.</string>
    <string name="not_logged_in">You have not logged in. Press the action button to login.</string>
    <string name="sync_merge_alert">Each entry that is pushed into the database contains a <b>unique id</b> that is kept <b>hidden</b> from the user. The entries that will be extracted from the QR codes will also contain <b>id</b>. In case of an <b>id conflict</b> would you like to <b>update</b> the existing entry with the imported entry\'s data(tag, username, password) or <b>create a new entry</b>?</string>


    <string-array name="about">

        <item>PassLoc is an open-source password manager application that uses sql-cipher to store data on your device.</item>
        <item>Needless to say that all the data stored in the database are encrypted with strong and reliable encryption.</item>
        <item>PassLoc does not store any data on the cloud. Hence, this app does not require an internet connection to function.</item>
        <item>The source code can be found at github.com/mubashirtanveerayon/PassLoc .</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="encryption">


        <item>PassLoc uses AES256 as the encryption algorithm. The sql-cipher library also relies on AES256.</item>
        <item>Your data is first encrypted using a special combination of the master and database password. Next, sql-cipher uses just the database password to encrypt the whole database file.</item>
        <item>When you add a new entry, the tag, username and password are encrypted individually using that special combination of passwords and then the data is pushed into the database along with a  unique id that is kept hidden from the user.</item>
        <item>If someone gains access to the password-protected database file, they will not be able to decrypt your data without your master password.</item>
        <item>This also means that if you happen to forget any of your passwords the database file becomes unusable.</item>



    </string-array>

    <string-array name="ui">


        <item>In this version of the app most of the ui-interactions are done using the floating action button and the bottom navigation panel.</item>

        <item>The access panel is for creating/logging into database files on your device.</item>
        <item>The view panel is for viewing the saved passwords.</item>
        <item>The Sync panel is used to save or sync data between databases created by PassLoc.</item>
        <item>The logout panel is used to logout(disconnect) from database.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sync">
        <item>Syncing(importing or exporting data) is done primarily using QR codes.</item>
        <item>Based on the amount of saved user credentials in the database table you are logged into, the number of QRCodes will vary.</item>
        <item>To import or export data you are needed to log in.</item>
        <item>You can import QR codes in two ways: from your gallery or scan using the device camera.</item>
        <item>You can generate QR codes for your current database and save it into the Download folder of your device.</item>

    </string-array>



</resources>